corporatehousingbyowner.com 2013-04-02

# Corporate Housing by owner: corporate housing and accommodations, furnished apartments for short term rentals

**Corporate Housing by Owner**

Your privacy is our priority at Corporate Housing by Owner, and we go to great lengths to protect it. Corporate Housing by Owner privacy policy covers the collection and use of personal information that may be collected by Corporate Housing by Owner anytime you interact with Corporate Housing by Owner, such as when you visit our website, when you purchase Corporate Housing by Owner services, or when you call our customer service associates.

**Why do we collect personal information?**  
Because it helps us deliver a superior level of customer service. It enables us to give you convenient access to our services and focus on categories of greatest interest to you. In addition, your personal information helps us keep you posted on the latest service announcements, special offers, and events that you might like to hear about.

If you choose not to be updated by Corporate Housing by Owner about the latest news, bookmark updates, and information on services click My Account  and update your personal contact information and preferences.

**What information do we collect?**  
There are a number of situations in which your personal information may help us give you better service. We may ask for your personal information when you're discussing a service issue on the phone with an associate, registering for a seminar, participating in an online survey, registering for our service, or purchasing a service. At such times, we may collect personal information relevant to the situation, such as your name, mailing address, phone number, email address, contact, preferences and credit card information, information about the Corporate Housing by Owner services you have purchased and information relating to a support or service issue. We collect information for market research purposes such as your occupation, where your property is located, and what area do you need corporate housing to gain a better understanding of our customers and thus provide more valuable service.

**When we disclose your personal information.**  
**Corporate Housing by Owner takes your privacy very seriously. Be assured that Corporate Housing by Owner does not sell or rent your contact information to other marketers.** To help us provide superior service, your personal information may be shared with legal entities within the Corporate Housing by Owner group globally who will safeguard it in accordance with Corporate Housing by Owner's privacy policy. There are also times when it may be advantageous for Corporate Housing by Owner to make certain personal information about you available to companies that Corporate Housing by Owner has a strategic relationship with or that perform work for Corporate Housing by Owner to provide products and services to you on our behalf. These companies may help us process information, extend credit, fulfill customer wishes, deliver services to you, manage and enhance customer data, provide customer service, assess your interest in our services, or conduct customer research or satisfaction surveys. These companies are also obligated to protect your personal information in accordance with Corporate Housing by Ownerâ€™s policies. Without such information being made available, it would be difficult for you to purchase products, have products delivered to you, receive customer service, provide us feedback to improve our services, or access certain services, offers, and content on the Corporate Housing by Owner's website. At times we may be required by law or litigation to disclose your personal information. We may also disclose information about you if we determine that for national security, law enforcement, or other issues of public importance, disclosure is necessary.

**How we protect your personal information.**  
Corporate Housing by Owner takes precautions including administrative, technical, and physical measures to safeguard your personal information against loss, theft, and misuse, as well as unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration, and destruction. Corporate Housing by Owner has safeguards in place to keep your personal information accurate, complete, and up to date for the purposes for which it is used. Naturally, you always have the right to access and correct the personal information you have provided. You can help us ensure that your contact information and preferences are accurate, complete, and up to date by checking at My Account  . You can also request a copy of your personal information, your product registration history, and your interactions with our sales and support agents by contacting us at the email address below.

**Cookies and other technologies**  
As is standard practice on many corporate websites, Corporate Housing by Owner's website uses cookies and other technologies to help us understand which parts of our websites are the most popular, where our visitors are going, and how much time they spend there. We also use cookies and other technologies to make sure that our online advertising is bringing customers to our services and to study traffic patterns on our website, to make it even more rewarding as well as to study the effectiveness of our customer communications. We use cookies to customize your experience and provide greater convenience each time you interact with us.  
By knowing your first name it lets us welcome you with a greeting the next time you visit the Corporate Housing by Owner Site. Information such as your country and language helps us provide a more useful online shopping experience.

If, however, you prefer not to enable cookies, Please note that certain features of the Corporate Housing by Owner website will not be available once cookies are disabled.

As is true of most Web sites, we gather certain information automatically and store it in log files. This information includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp, and clickstream data.

We use this information, which does not identify individual users, to analyze trends, to administer the site, to track users movements around the site and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole. Corporate Housing by Owner will not use the information collected to market directly to that person. In some of our email messages we use a click-through URL linked to content on the Corporate Housing by Owner website. When a customer clicks one of these URLs, they pass through our web server before arriving at the destination web page. We track this click-through data to help us determine interest in particular topics and measure the effectiveness of our customer communications. If you prefer not to be tracked simply avoid clicking text or graphic links in the email.

In addition we use pixel tags tiny graphic images to tell us what parts of our website customers have visited or to measure the effectiveness of searches customers perform on our site. Pixel tags also enable us to send email messages in a format customers can read. And they tell us whether emails have been opened to assure that were only sending messages that are of interest to our customers. We store all of this information in a secure database located in Highlands Ranch, Colorado in the United States.

**Our company wide commitment to your privacy**  
As we said, Corporate Housing by Owner takes protecting your privacy very seriously. To make sure your personal information is secure, we communicate these guidelines to Corporate Housing by Owner employees and strictly enforce privacy safeguards within the company. We do not knowingly solicit personal information from minors or send them requests for personal information. Corporate Housing by Owner's website has links to the sites of other companies. Corporate Housing by Owner is not responsible for their privacy practices. We encourage you to learn about the privacy policies of those companies.

**Privacy questions**  
If you have questions or concerns about Corporate Housing by Owner's Customer Privacy Policy or data processing, please use the information (see list below) to contact us. The Corporate Housing by Owner team in will respond to your inquiry within 48 hours.

**Mailing Address:**  
Corporate Housing by Owner  
9249 South Broadway #200 - 416  
Highlands Ranch, CO 80129

Email: [Support](mailto:support@mychbo.com)   
Business Line: 720.238.3068 M-F 8-5MST  
Toll Free: 877.333.2426  
Fax: 720.228.2426

If you do not want Corporate Housing by Owner to keep you up to date with Corporate Housing by Owner news, software updates and the latest information on products and services click My Account  and update your personal contact information and preferences. Naturally, if you notify us that you do not want us to use your information for a particular purpose, we will not do so.

Corporate Housing by Owner may update its privacy policy from time to time. When we change the policy in a material way a notice will be posted on our website along with the updated privacy policy. Corporate Housing by Owner, 9249 South Broadway #200-416, Highlands Ranch, Colorado, USA, 80129

Last updated May 16, 2008  
Corporate Housing by Owner, All rights reserved.

|
